Harold H. Burton Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Supreme Court File, 1792-1965 (Box 56-325)
  - Case File, 1944-1960 (Box 125-308)
    - October term 1948 (Box 166)
      - Opinions
        - Appellate docket
          - Commissioner v. Wodehouse, 84; (4 folders); (7 folders) (Box 177)
          - Krulewitch v. United States, 143
          - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Crompton-Highland Mills, 197; (5 folders); (2 folders) (Box 178)
          - United States v. Penn Foundry & Mfg. Co., 253; (7 folders)
          - Interstate Oil Pipeline Co. v. Stone, 287; (3 folders)
          - California v. Zook, 355; (5 folders); (10 folders) (Box 179)
          - United States v. Wittek, 473; (3 folders); (4 folders) (Box 180)
          - Federal Power Comm'n v. Panhandle E. Pipe Line Co., 558
    - October term 1949
      - Conference lists, 1949-1950, (6 folders)
      - Dockets
        - Appellate
          - Index
          - 1-199, (2 folders)
          - 200-850, (7 folders) (Box 181)
        - Miscellaneous, 1-568, (2 folders)
      - Law clerks' memoranda
        - Appellate docket
          - Argued cases
            - 1-29, (5 folders)
            - 31-513, (14 folders) (Box 182)
            - 568-847 (Box 183)
          - Certiorari denied and appeals dismissed
            - 52-442, (15 folders)
            - 443-838, (13 folders) (Box 184)
        - Miscellaneous docket
          - 1-65, (2 folders)
          - 66-559, (13 folders) (Box 185)
        - Original docket, 12-13
      - Opinions (Box 186)
        - Appellate docket
          - United States v. Kansas City Life Ins. Co., 1; (9 folders)
          - United States ex rel. Eichenlaub v. Shaughnessy, 3; (6 folders)
          - McGrath v. Manufacturers Trust Co., 11; (6 folders) (Box 187)
          - Manufacturers Trust Co. v. McGrath See same container, 11, 15
          - Henderson v. United States, 25; (5 folders); (2 folders) (Box 188)
          - United States v. Westinghouse Elec. & Mfg. Co., 26
          - Oakley v. Louisville & Nashville R.R., 28; (5 folders)
          - Haynes v. Cincinnati, New Orleans & Texas Pac. Ry. See same container, 28, 29
          - United States v. Benedict, 45; (4 folders); (7 folders) (Box 189)
          - Savorgnan v. United States, 48; (8 folders)
          - Darr v. Burford, 51; (3 folders) (Box 190)
          - Manufacturers Trust Co. v. Becker, 55; (2 folders)
          - O'Donnell v. Elgin, Joliet & E. Ry., 56; (2 folders)
          - Creel v. Lone Star Defense Corp. See same container, 96, 58
          - Aaron v. Ford, Bacon & Davis, Inc. See same container, 96, 79
          - United States ex rel. Willumeit v. Shaughnessy See Container 186, 3, 82
          - Powell v. United States Cartridge Co., 96; (5 folders); (1 folder) (Box 191, Box 192)
          - Standard Oil Co. v. Federal Trade Comm'n See also Container 199, 1, 107; (3 folders)
          - Capitol Greyhound Lines v. Brice, 118
          - United Mine Workers v. United States, 169
          - District of Columbia v. Little, 302; (2 folders)
          - Railway Labor Executives' Ass'n v. United States, 337; (6 folders)
          - Hiatt v. Brown, 359; (2 folders) (Box 193)
          - Hubsch v. United States, 379
          - Schweitzer v. United States See same container, 379, 380
    - October term 1950
      - Conference lists, 1950-1951, (6 folders)
      - Dockets
        - Appellate
          - Index
          - 1-600, (6 folders)
          - 601-769, unnumbered, (2 folders) (Box 194)
        - Miscellaneous, 1-532, (2 folders)
        - Original, 8-10
      - Law clerks' memoranda
        - Appellate docket
          - Argued cases
            - 1-133, (11 folders)
            - 134-600, (14 folders) (Box 195)
          - Certiorari denied and appeals dismissed
            - 26-92, (2 folders)
            - 94-402, (14 folders) (Box 196)
            - 403-672, (15 folders) (Box 197)
            - 678-756, unnumbered, (3 folders) (Box 198)
        - Miscellaneous docket
          - 2-393, (11 folders)
          - 394-532, (4 folders) (Box 199)
        - Original docket, 5-13
      - Opinions
        - Appellate docket
          - Standard Oil Co. v. Federal Trade Comm'n See also Container 192, 107, 1; (8 folders); (2 folders); (5 folders) (Box 200, Box 201)
          - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship v. McGrath See same container, 8, 7 (Box 202)
          - Joint Anti-Fascist Refugee Comm. v. McGrath, 8; (10 folders); (6 folders) (Box 203)
          - Bailey v. Richardson See Container 202, 8, 49
          - International Workers Order v. McGrath See Container 202, 8, 71
          - Local 74, United Bhd. of Carpenters v. National Labor Relations Bd., 85; (5 folders)
          - International Bhd. of Elec. Workers Local 501 v. National Labor Relations Bd., 108; (1 folder); (5 folders) (Box 204)
          - Spector Motor Serv. v. O'Connor, 132; (5 folders); (1 folder) (Box 205)
          - United States v. Pewee Coal Co., 168
          - Capital Transit Co. v. United States See same container, 218, 204
          - Niagara Hudson Power Corp. v. Leventritt, 211; (8 folders)
          - Securities & Exchange Comm'n v. Leventritt See same container, 211, 212
          - Collins v. Hardyman, 217
          - United States v. Yellow Cab Co., 218; (3 folders); (6 folders) (Box 206)
          - Zittman v. McGrath, 298
          - Zittman v. McGrath See same container, 298, 299
          - National Labor Relations Bd. v. International Rice Milling Co., 313; (6 folders)
          - McCarthy v. McGrath See same container, 298, 314
          - McCarthy v. McGrath See same container, 298, 315
          - McCloskey v. McGrath See same container, 298, 324
          - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Denver Bldg. & Constr. Trades Council, 393; (2 folders); (11 folders) (Box 207)
          - Garner v. Board of Pub. Works, 453; (3 folders)
    - October term 1951 (Box 208)
      - Conference lists, 1951-1952, (8 folders)
      - Dockets
        - Appellate
          - Index
          - 1-600, (6 folders)
          - 601-828, (2 folders) (Box 209)
        - Miscellaneous, nos. 1-519
      - Law clerks' memoranda
        - Appellate docket
          - Argued cases
            - 1-151, (11 folders)
            - 158-624, (15 folders) (Box 210)
            - 649-762 (Box 211)
          - Certiorari denied and appeals dismissed
            - 4-346, (14 folders)
            - 347-685, (15 folders) (Box 212)
            - 688-814, unnumbered, (3 folders) (Box 213)
        - Miscellaneous docket
          - 1-430, (12 folders)
          - 431-517, (2 folders) (Box 214)
        - Original docket, 5-8
      - Opinions
        - Appellate docket
          - Lorain Journal Co. v. United States, 26; (7 folders); (2 folders) (Box 215)
          - Carlson v. Landon, 35; (5 folders)
          - Perkins v. Benguet Consol. Mining Co., 85; (7 folders); (4 folders) (Box 216)
          - Butterfield v. Zydok See Container 215, 35, 136
          - Lilly v. Commissioner, 158; (6 folders)
          - Lykes v. United States, 173; (2 folders); (4 folders) (Box 217)
          - Rutkin v. United States, 195; (5 folders)
          - Public Utils. Comm'n v. Pollak, 224; (6 folders) (Box 218)
          - Pillsbury v. United Eng'g Co., 229; (4 folders)
          - Pollak v. Public Utils. Comm'n See same container, 224, 295
          - Madsen v. Kinsella, 411; (2 folders); (8 folders) (Box 219)
          - Isbrandtsen Co. v. Johnson, 493; (5 folders)
          - McGee v. Ekberg See Container 230, 32, 517 (Box 220)
          - Lee v. United States, 543; (2 folders)
          - Daniels v. Allen See Container 230, 32, 626
          - Speller v. Allen See Container 230, 32, 643
          - United States v. Baldi See Container 230, 32, 669
          - Brown v. Allen See Container 230, 32, 670
          - Youngstown Sheet and Tube Co. v. Sawyer, 744; (10 folders); (5 folders) (Box 221)
          - Sawyer v. Youngstown Sheet and Tube Co. See Container 220, 744, 745
    - October term 1952 (Box 222)
      - Applications, 1952-1953
      - Conference lists, 1952-1953, (7 folders)
      - Dockets
        - Appellate
          - Index
          - 1-700, (7 folders)
          - 701-850, unnumbered, (2 folders) (Box 223)
        - Miscellaneous
          - 1-553, Special Term no. 1, (2 folders)
      - Law clerks' memoranda
        - Appellate docket
          - Argued cases
            - 3-53, (10 folders)
            - 60-442, (16 folders) (Box 224)
            - 444-648, (6 folders) (Box 225)
          - Certiorari denied and appeals dismissed
            - 4-263, (9 folders)
            - 264-590, (16 folders) (Box 226)
            - 591-845, unnumbered, (8 folders) (Box 227)
        - Miscellaneous docket
          - 2-263, (8 folders)
          - 264-553, unnumbered, (9 folders) (Box 228)
        - Original docket, 5-11, unnumbered
      - Opinions
        - Appellate docket
          - King v. United States, 9; (5 folders) (Box 229)
          - United States v. Henning, 10; (2 folders)
          - Kwong Hai Chew v. Colding, 17; (7 folders) (Box 230)
          - Daniels v. Adams See same container, 32, 20
          - Speller v. Allen See same container, 32, 22
          - United States v. Baldi See same container, 32, 31
          - Brown v. Allen, 32; (7 folders); (2 folders) (Box 231)
          - American Newspaper Publishers Ass'n v. National Labor Relations Bd., 53; (7 folders); (1 folder) (Box 232)
          - Local 10, United Ass'n of Journeymen Plumbers & Steamfitters v. Graham, 86; (5 folders)
          - Ford Motor Co. v. Huffman, 193; (5 folders); (3 folders) (Box 233)
          - United Auto. Workers v. Huffman See Container 232, 193, 194
          - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Gamble Enters., 238; (6 folders)
          - May v. Anderson, 244; (3 folders); (5 folders) (Box 234)
          - Polizzi v. Cowles Magazines, 287; (2 folders)
          - Watson v. Commissioner, 290; (5 folders)
          - Times-Picayune Publishing Co. v. United States, 374; (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 235)
          - United States v. Times-Picayune Publishing Co. See Container 234, 374, 375
          - Wells v. Simonds Abrasive Co., 394 (Box 236)
          - Transcontinental & W. Air v. Koppal, 509; (5 folders)
          - Bridges v. United States See also Container 237, 634, 548; (6 folders); (4 folders) (Box 237)
          - United States v. Grainger See also Container 236, 548, 634; (6 folders); (1 folder) (Box 238)
          - United States v. Clavere See Container 236, 634, 635
          - United States v. Clavere See Container 236, 634, 636
          - Rosenberg v. United States, 687; (3 folders)
          - Sobell v. United States See same container, 687, 719
    - October term, 1953
      - Applications, 1953-1954
      - Conference lists, 1953-1954, (7 folders)
      - Dockets
        - Appellate
          - Index
          - 1-299, (3 folders)
          - 300-800, unnumbered, (5 folders) (Box 239)
        - Miscellaneous, 1-630, (2 folders)
      - Law clerks' memoranda
        - Appellate docket
          - Argued cases
            - 5-87, (9 folders)
            - 92-635, (14 folders) (Box 240)
          - Certiorari denied or appeals dismissed
            - 3-110, (3 folders)
            - 111-417, (17 folders) (Box 241)
            - 418-690, (16 folders) (Box 242)
            - 693-797, (3 folders) (Box 243)
        - Miscellaneous docket
          - 3-492, (14 folders)
          - 493-621, (3 folders) (Box 244)
        - Original docket, unnumbered
      - Opinions
        - Appellate docket
          - Brown v. Board of Educ. See also Container 257, 1, 1; (3 folders)
          - Briggs v. Elliott See same container, 1, 2
          - Davis v. County School Bd. See same container, 1, 4
          - Bolling v. Sharpe See same container, 1, 8
          - Gebhart v. Bolton See same container, 1, 10
          - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Local 1229, Int'l Bhd. of Elec. Workers, 15; (6 folders); (2 folders) (Box 245)
          - Toolson v. New York Yankees, 18; (4 folders)
          - Kowalski v. Chandler See same container, 18, 23
          - Corbett v. Chandler See same container, 18, 25
          - Federal Power Comm'n v. Niagara Mohawk Power Corp., 28; (4 folders); (5 folders) (Box 246)
          - Salsburg v. Maryland, 38; (4 folders); (2 folders) (Box 247)
          - Avondale Marine Ways, Inc. v. Henderson, 44
          - Barsky v. Board of Regents, 69; (7 folders)
          - United Constr. Workers v. Laburnum Constr. Corp., 188; (3 folders); (4 folders) (Box 248)
          - Alaska S.S. Co. v. Petterson, 287; (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 249)
          - United States v. Shaughnessy, 366
          - Walters v. City of St. Louis, 389
          - Allen v. Grand Cent. Aircraft Co., 450; (10 folders); (1 folder) (Box 250)
        - Original docket
          - Alabama v. Texas, --
          - Rhode Island v. Louisiana See same container, Alabama v. Texas, --
    - October term 1954
      - Applications, 1954-1955
      - Conference lists, 1954-1955, (7 folders)
      - Dockets
        - Appellate
          - Index
          - 1-400, (4 folders)
          - 401-840, unnumbered, (5 folders) (Box 251)
        - Miscellaneous, 1-691, (2 folders)
      - Law clerks' memoranda
        - Appellate docket
          - Argued cases
            - 1-28, (9 folders)
            - 29-251, (17 folders) (Box 252)
            - 261-616, (8 folders) (Box 253)
          - Certiorari denied and appeals dismissed
            - 12-192, (8 folders)
            - 193-483, (17 folders) (Box 254)
            - 484-768, (17 folders) (Box 255)
            - 769-840, unnumbered (Box 256)
        - Miscellaneous docket
          - 2-420, (16 folders)
          - 422-691, unnumbered, (9 folders) (Box 257)
      - Opinions
        - Appellate docket
          - Brown v. Board of Educ. See also Container 244, 1, 1; (5 folders); (2 folders) (Box 258)
          - Briggs v. Elliott See Container 257, 1, 2
          - Davis v. County School Bd. See Container 257, 1, 3
          - Bolling v. Sharpe See Container 257, 1, 4
          - Gebhart v. Belton See Container 257, 1, 5
          - United States v. Guy W. Capps, Inc., 14; (7 folders)
          - National Union of Marine Cooks v. Arnold, 19; (6 folders) (Box 259)
          - Commissioner v. Estate of Sternberger, 24; (9 folders)
          - United States v. Koppers Co., 29; (11 folders) (Box 260)
          - Premier Oil Ref. Co. of Texas v. United States See same container, 29, 41
          - Federal Power Comm'n v. Colorado Interstate Gas Co., 45; (2 folders); (6 folders) (Box 261)
          - Gonzales v. United States, 69
          - Boston Metals Co. v. S.S. Winding Gulf, 70
          - Ryan Stevedoring Co. v. Pan-Atlantic S.S. Corp. See Container 272, 4, 157
          - United States v. Nielson, 210
          - Diehl v. Lehigh Valley R.R., 246
          - Maneja v. Waialua Agricultural Co., 357; (2 folders); (6 folders) (Box 262)
          - Waialua Agricultural Co. v. Maneja See Container 261, 357, 358
          - Federal Power Comm'n v. Oregon, 367; (3 folders); (5 folders) (Box 263)
        - Original docket
          - Texas v. New Mexico, 9 Orig.
    - October term 1955
      - Applications, 1955-1956
      - Conference lists
        - 1955, Oct., (1 folder)
        - 1955, Oct., (2 folders) (Box 264)
        - 1955, Nov.-1956, June, (6 folders)
      - Dockets
        - Appellate
          - Index
          - 1-500, (5 folders)
          - 501-994, unnumbered, (5 folders) (Box 265)
        - Miscellaneous, 1-802, (3 folders)
        - Original, 11-14, unnumbered
      - Law clerks' memoranda
        - Appellate docket
          - Argued cases
            - 3-28, (7 folders)
            - 29-257, (16 folders) (Box 266)
            - 278-713, (9 folders) (Box 267)
          - Certiorari denied and appeals dismissed
            - 1-178, (7 folders)
            - 179-461, (16 folders) (Box 268)
            - 462-708, (14 folders) (Box 269)
            - 709-994, (11 folders) (Box 270)
          - Per Curiam reversals, certiorari granted, and appeals allowed, nos. 40-915, (2 folders)
        - Miscellaneous docket
          - 1-57, (2 folders)
          - 58-741, (16 folders) (Box 271)
          - 742-799, unnumbered (Box 272)
          - Per Curiam reversals, certiorari granted, and appeals allowed, 28-371, unnumbered
        - Original docket, 7-14
      - Opinions
        - Appellate docket
          - Ryan Stevedoring Co. v. Pan-Atlantic S.S. Corp., 4; (7 folders)
          - Mastro Plastics Corp. v. National Labor Relations Bd., 19; (1 folder); (8 folders) (Box 273)
          - United States v. Twin City Power Co., 21; (6 folders); (4 folders) (Box 274)
          - Sears, Roebuck & Co. v. Mackey For additional material see Container 275, 76, 34; (8 folders)
          - Communist Party v. Subversive Activities Control Bd., 48; (3 folders)
          - Bernhardt v. Polygraphic Co. of Am., 49 (Box 275)
          - Costello v. United States, 72; (2 folders)
          - Cold Metal Process Co. v. United Eng'g & Foundry Co., 76; (8 folders)
          - International Harvester Credit Corp. v. Goodrich, 82; (2 folders); (5 folders) (Box 276)
          - Griffin v. Illinois, 95; (3 folders)
          - Frozen Food Express v. United States See same container, 162, 158
          - Interstate Commerce Comm'n v. Frozen Food Express See same container, 162, 159
          - American Trucking Ass'ns v. Frozen Food Express See same container, 162, 160
          - Akron, Canton & Youngstown R.R. v. Frozen Food Express See same container, 162, 161
          - East Tex. Motor Freight Lines v. Frozen Food Express, 162; (2 folders)
          - Interstate Commerce Comm'n v. Frozen Food Express See same container, 162, 163
          - Akron, Canton & Youngstown R.R. v. Frozen Food Express See same container, 162, 164
          - Chessman v. Teets See Container 293, 893, 196
          - United Mine Workers v. Arkansas Oak Flooring Co., 227; (5 folders); (2 folders) (Box 277)
          - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Lion Oil Co., 241
          - United States ex rel. Darcy v. Handy, 323; (5 folders)
          - Petrowski v. Hawkeye-Security Ins. Co., 469; (3 folders)
          - Durley v. Mayo, 489; (3 folders) (Box 278)
    - October term 1956
      - Applications, 1956-1957
      - Conference lists, 1956-1957, (10 folders)
      - Dockets
        - Appellate
          - Index
          - 1-99
          - 100-1108, unnumbered, (10 folders) (Box 279)
        - Miscellaneous, 1-838, (3 folders)
        - Original, 12-14
      - Law clerks' memoranda
        - Appellate docket
          - 1-5, (2 folders)
          - 6-71, (15 folders) (Box 280)
          - 72-228, (14 folders) (Box 281)
          - 229-420, (15 folders) (Box 282)
          - 421-647, (16 folders) (Box 283)
          - 648-978, (15 folders) (Box 284)
          - 979-1090, unnumbered, (2 folders) (Box 285)
        - Miscellaneous docket
          - 1-567, (13 folders)
          - 568-838, (7 folders) (Box 286)
        - Original docket, 2-14, (4 folders)
      - Opinions
        - Appellate docket
          - United States v. E. I. du Pont de Nemours & Co., 3; (4 folders); (5 folders) (Box 287)
          - Walker v. City of Hutchinson, 13; (2 folders)
          - United States v. Bergh, 17; (7 folders)
          - Jencks v. United States, 23; (4 folders) (Box 288)
          - Scales v. United States, 29; (3 folders)
          - Lightfoot v. United States See same container, 29, 32
          - Paoli v. United States, 33; (5 folders)
          - Nilva v. United States, 37; (1 folder); (5 folders) (Box 289)
          - Amalgamated Meat Cutters Local 427 v. Fairlawn Meats See Container 291, 280, 41
          - United States ex rel. Sherman v. Carter, 48; (6 folders)
          - San Diego Bldg. Trades Council v. Garmon See Container 291, 280, 50 (Box 290)
          - Roviaro v. United States, 58; (8 folders)
          - Libson Shops v. Koehler, 64; (5 folders)
          - Lehmann v. United States ex rel. Carson, 72
          - Automobile Club of Mich. v. Commissioner, 89 (Box 291)
          - Textile Workers Union v. Lincoln Mills of Ala., 211; (4 folders)
          - Haynes v. United States, 257; (2 folders)
          - Curcio v. United States, 260; (2 folders)
          - Goodall-Sanford, Inc. v. United Textile Workers See same container, 211, 262
          - General Elec. Co. v. Local 205, United Elec. Workers See same container, 211, 276
          - Guss v. National Labor Relations Bd., 280; (5 folders)
          - United States v. Turley, 289; (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box 292)
          - United States v. Calamaro, 304
          - Baltimore & Ohio Ry. v. Jackson, 370; (5 folders)
          - California v. Taylor, 385; (5 folders); (2 folders) (Box 293)
          - Pan-Atlantic S.S. Corp. v. Atlantic Coast Line R.R., 408
          - Interstate Commerce Comm'n v. Atlantic Coast Line R.R. See same container, 408, 424
          - Mulcahey v. Catalanotte See Container 290, 72, 435
          - Morey v. Dowd, 475; (6 folders)
          - Chessman v. Teets, 893
          - McBride v. Toledo Terminal R.R., 972
        - Original docket
          - Wisconsin v. Illinois, 2 Orig.; (2 folders)
          - Michigan v. Illinois See same container, 2 Orig., 3 Orig.
          - New York v. Illinois See same container, 2 Orig., 4 Orig.
    - October term 1957
      - Applications, 1957-1958
      - Conference lists
        - 1957, Oct., (3 folders)
        - 1957, Nov.-1958, June, (5 folders) (Box 294)
      - Dockets
        - Appellate
          - Index
          - 1-800, (8 folders)
          - 801-1095, unnumbered, (3 folders) (Box 295)
        - Miscellaneous, 1-874, (3 folders)
        - Original, 9
      - Law clerks' memoranda
        - Appellate docket
          - 1-33, (9 folders)
          - 34-104, (15 folders) (Box 296)
          - 105-263, (16 folders) (Box 297)
          - 264-480, (16 folders) (Box 298)
          - 481-737, (16 folders) (Box 299)
          - 738-1103, (16 folders) (Box 300)
    - October term 1957 (Box 301)
      - Law clerks' memoranda
        - Miscellaneous docket
          - 1-424, (16 folders)
          - 425-874, (10 folders) (Box 302)
        - Original docket, 2-12
      - Opinions
        - Appellate docket
          - Scales v. United States See Container 288, 29, 3
          - Lightfoot v. United States See Container 288, 29, 4
          - Youngdahl v. Rainfair, Inc., 11; (2 folders); (4 folders) (Box 303)
          - United Auto. Workers v. Russell, 21; (7 folders); (4 folders) (Box 304)
          - United States v. Central Eureka Mining Co., 29; (6 folders)
          - United States v. Sharpnack, 35; (6 folders) (Box 305)
          - Moore v. Michigan, 42; (4 folders)
          - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Wooster Div. of Borg-Warner Corp., 53; (4 folders) (Box 306)
          - Beilan v. Board of Pub. Educ., 63; (5 folders); (3 folders) (Box 307)
          - Gunn v. Ohm, 73
          - Wooster Div. of Borg-Warner Corp. v. National Labor Relations Bd. See Container 305, 53, 78
          - McAllister v. Magnolia Petroleum Co., 83
          - Fidelity-Philadelphia Trust Co. v. Smith, 130
          - Ashdown v. Utah, 158; (4 folders)
          - Rosenbloom v. United States, 451
    - August special term 1958
      - Opinions
        - Appellate docket
          - Cooper v. Aaron, 1; (6 folders) (Box 308)
        - Miscellaneous docket
          - Aaron v. Cooper See Container 307, 1, 1 Misc.
    - October term 1958
      - Applications, 1958
      - Conference lists, 1958, (3 folders)
    - October term 1959
      - Miscellaneous opinions, 1959-1960
  - Miscellany, 1792-1964 (Box 308-325)